MRS. WOLOWITZ: You're right.
When you're right, you're right.
-What if they're out of the Le Sueur?
-Then get the regular!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
All right. You don't have to yell.
[DOOR CLOSES]
(Howard:)Sorry about that.
[CELL PHONE CHIMING]
(Bernadette(her phone chimes):)-Let me just put that on vibrate.
-I'm already on vibrate.
[MAKES VIBRATING SOUND]
Okay, now, that one I got.
(Bernadette:)Howard, did you say something
to Leonard about me?
(Howard:)What do you mean?
(Bernadette:)He says if I go see his experiment
tomorrow, it might weird you out.
(Howard:)Really? He said that?
(Bernadette:)-You're not jealous of Leonard, are you?
-Me? No.
(Howard:)I may have mentioned
that it's a little inappropriate...
(Howard:)...to be asking another man's girlfriend
to his experiment...
...without discussing it with said man.
(Bernadette:)I need to ask your permission
to hang out with Leonard?
(Howard:)I didn't say anything like that.
I said Leonard has to ask my permission.